let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What type of galaxy is the most common in the universe?",
    answer: "Elliptical galaxies",
    options: [
      "Elliptical galaxies",
      "Spiral galaxies",
      "Regular galaxies",
      "Irregular galaxies"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What percent of the universe is dark matter?",
    answer: "27%",
    options: [
      "17%",
      "27%",
      "37%",
      "47%"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is the most common type of star found in the Milky Way?",
    answer: "Red dwarf stars",
    options: [
      "Neutron stars",
      "Red dwarf stars",
      "Main Sequence stars",
      "Supergiant stars"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the longest continuous time a human has spent in space?",
    answer: "437 days",
    options: [
      "347 days",
      "374 days",
      "437 days",
      "473 days"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is the diameter of the Earth's moon?",
    answer: "2,159 miles",
    options: [
      "2,159 miles",
      "1,592 miles",
      "5,921 miles",
      "9,215 miles"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the coldest place in the universe?",
    answer: "The Boomerang Nebula",
    options: [
        "The Dark Side of the Moon",
        "The Boomerang Nebula",
        "The Cold Atom Lab",
        "Pluto"
    ]
   },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "How many planets are in the Solar System?",
    answer: "Eight planets",
    options: [
        "Seven planets",
        "Eight planets",
        "Nine planets",
        "Ten planets"
    ]
   },
   {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is the largest type of star in the universe?",
    answer: "Red supergiant stars",
    options: [
        "Red supergiant stars",
        "Sun",
        "T Tauri stars",
        "Main Sequence stars"
    ]
   },
   {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is the farthest distance from Earth a manned mission has traveled?",
    answer: "248,655 miles",
    options: [
        "246,855 miles",
        "248,655 miles",
        "264,855 miles",
        "268,455 miles"
    ]
   },
   {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is the largest crater on Earth's moon?",
    answer: "South Pole - Aitken basin",
    options: [
        "Mare Imbrium",
        "Moltke",
        "South Pole - Aitken basin",
        "Tycho"
    ]
   },
   {
    numb: 11,
    question: "The hottest place in the universe is located in which constellation?",
    answer: "The constellation Virgo",
    options: [
        "The constellation Virgo",
        "The constellation Orion",
        "The constellation Scorpius",
        "The constellation Ursa Major"
    ]
   },
   {
    numb: 12,
    question: "What is the largest planet in our solar system?",
    answer: "Jupiter",
    options: [
        "Earth",
        "Venus",
        "Jupiter",
        "Mars"
    ]
   },
   {
    numb: 13,
    question: "What is the closest star to the Sun?",
    answer: "Proxima Centauri",
    options: [
        "Proxima Centauri",
        "Barnard's Star",
        "Lalande",
        "Luyten's Star"
    ]
   },
   {
    numb: 14,
    question: "How many minutes was the shortest space flight?",
    answer: "15 minutes",
    options: [
        "45 minutes",
        "35 minutes",
        "25 minutes",
        "15 minutes"
    ]
   },
   {
    numb: 15,
    question: "What are the dimensions in inches of the first footprint on Earth's moon?",
    answer: "13 by 6 inches",
    options: [
        "13 by 6 inches",
        "13 by 5 inches",
        "13 by 4 inches",
        "13 by 3 inches"
    ]
   },
   {
    numb: 16,
    question: "How old is the universe in years?",
    answer: "13,8 billion years old",
    options: [
        "31,8 billion years old",
        "18,3 billion yearws old",
        "38,1 billion years old",
        "13,8 billion years old"
    ]
   },
   {
    numb: 17,
    question: "What is the smallest planet in our solar system?",
    answer: "Mercury",
    options: [
        "Pluto",
        "Mars",
        "Earth",
        "Mercury"
    ]
   },
   {
    numb: 18,
    question: "Which NASA space flight was the last manned mission to the moon?",
    answer: "Apollo 17",
    options: [
        "Apollo 1",
        "Apollo 11",
        "Apollo 13",
        "Apollo 17"
    ]
   },
   {
    numb: 19,
    question: "How many moons are in our Solar System?",
    answer: "181 moons",
    options: [
        "151 moons",
        "161 moons",
        "171 moons",
        "181 moons"
    ]
   },
   {
    numb: 20,
    question: "What flavor ice cream did Baskin-Robbins release in 1969 to commemorate America's landing on the moon?",
    answer: "Lunar Cheesecake",
    options: [
        "Lunar Biscuit",
        "Lunar Apple Pie",
        "Lunar Cheesecake",
        "Lunar Chocolate"
    ]
   },
];